# **AKSHITHRAJ UTTAM**



#### Personal

Address

Warangal urban, Hanamakonda Telangana state 506001 Hanamakonda

Phone number 6302133646

Email akshithraj5@gmail.com Energetic Web designer with 2 years experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive and responsive websites or Startups of there innovation ideas I.e

Educational, Photography Personal Portfolios. Clear Understanding of modern technologies and best practices Experience le with VS Studio and I believe learning is important because exploreing new gaining new technology never make us worthless

(PERONSAL PORTFOLIO: <a href="https://akshithraj.netlify.app/">https://akshithraj.netlify.app/</a>)

## Work experience

Website Developer

Feb 2019 - Jan 2021

VIBAFOUNDATION, Warangal, Telangana

I was one of the innovation fellow in the viba foundation I worked in web team and marketing team and I'm so passionate towards web development because trying until getting a responsive output i like more because true hard work never make us worthless

Business Development intern Edubenchers, Surat, Gujarat Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

I was worked in edubenchers has intern in business development and I personally learned from this intern is expanding a certain company standards to large rsector

### **Education and Qualifications**

BTech cse

Sep 2019 - Mar 2023

Vaagdevi college of engineering, Warangal

Intermediate

Jun 2017 - Mar 2019

Alphores Junior College, Warangal

SSC

Jun 2003 - Mar 2017

Tejaswi high school, Warangal

### Skills

HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP

••••

JAVASCRIPT

••••

NODE JS

....

MARKETING PHP MYSQL

....

#### Achievements

I participated in NASA SPACE APP CHALLENGE 2020 I done a website with a theme how to reduce pollution in India